[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tokyo Stock Exchange"]}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "Kyung, what is the latest over there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, let's start with the Tokyo Stock Exchange.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "What the hell is going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "All right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "It's not just an American problem, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "No, it isn't an American problem and it is everyone's problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Eastern Time"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "They really didn't get it, did they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Well, if he was hoping to reassure investors out there, Piers, he failed because when he started speaking just before 2:00 Eastern Time here in the United States, the Dow was down about 400 points.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "And shouldn't the senior politicians be reconvening to deal with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "It certainly is a national emergency right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Ali, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Yes, you're exactly -- you're exactly right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Don't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "They do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Wolf, yes or no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Erin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Ali?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Asia"]}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "ORGAN: Kyung?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "People in Asia think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["50 percent"]}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "And if we are facing this catastrophe, what can President Obama do about it to stop it from happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Well, the probability of a double dip recession right now, in my view, is at least 50 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "And storms don't get much bigger than this, do they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "They don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Soros"]}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Do you that if there are other people out there making a killing as everybody else loses?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I cannot speak to Mr. Soros.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Yes or no, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "I think a double dip reselling is at this point very likely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Mohamed El-Erian, yes or no, double dip recession?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "CC", "DT", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "High risk can be averted, but a high risk.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "How should people take care of their money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Well, the first thing you have to do is not sell into a falling market.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "But the bad news is the value of those 401(k)s has been sliding, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "CD", "NN", ":", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "And here's the worst news.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Is it happening again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "What's your gut feeling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "My gut feeling tells me we're in for a little bit of a rough ride.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "What would you like to hear from him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I actually had a conversation with my wife about this over the week.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Could you see that coming to America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Let's be clear, we're a long way from that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "How bad is this from your point of view, from a guy that runs a big company in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Quite frankly, economic weakness is a time of opportunity, if you're prepared for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "How do you reenergize the jobs market?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Well, obviously it starts with confidence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "With a straight face then, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Pacific"]}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "What is the global perspective?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "The reason that the Asian markets and the South Pacific markets are lower is quite simply, having seen such a dramatic fall on Wall Street, there was no way they can stand as a bulwark against that tidal wave of selling and market turmoil.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "I suppose the obvious question I want to put to you is how much of this is just opportunistic gangsterism, if you like, by disaffected youth, and how much of it is indicative of an underlying social problem caused by the financial malaise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I think whatever it started out as on Saturday night, after the shooting earlier last week by the police of someone -- I think whatever it started out as has long since gone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "How do you see things going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Piers, I have the shirt on my back and I have managed to keep it there for all these years because I've never given a prediction on where the market is going.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Yes, I think in some places we are heading for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Is this an unwinnable war now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "You know, I mean, it is like the war on crime.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "What affect will that have on the moral there for the American military?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "MD", "IN", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Well, I think for the SEAL community, it's a very tight community.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "As you say, when you're seeing ten years on, the rangers and the SEALs really struggling, it should send a message, shouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Are there any tangible things that we can identify that have been progress made, if you like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Kyung, where are we right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Well, what started off as a bad day, Piers, is starting to look even worse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Is it going to get worse and worse, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Traders are certainly bracing for that, that this is just the beginning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]